

Applicant for:

Java Developer (Spring boot) ~1200\$

Dr.JOY 15 July 2020

Toan

★ toankingfantasy@gmail.com

Main interests: Java, Spring

Please answer our following questions

- 1. Why do you want to work at Dr.JOY company?
- 2. What are your salary requirements?
- 3. How many years of experience do you have? When was the last time you worked with java spring?

Note from ITviec: Toan skipped the cover letter.



Full Name: NGUYEN VAN TOAN
Tel Phone: +84356 071 008
Date of birth: 12/02/1991

E-mail: toanbkfet@gmail.com Current Address: Hanoi city, VietNam

Summary

Software Engineer with experience in all levels of testing, software architecture design, analysis functional requirements, coding.

Skill Highlights

Agile/Scrum methodology

Java

- Linux
- PostgreSQL and GridDB database

Language

- Japanese N5
- Can speak or write mail by English in work to communicate with customers

Experience

08/2014 to 06/2017

Toshiba Software Development VietNam

- Take part in development Network Attached Storage (NAS) for server system:
- Develop kernel on Operating System Debian 6.0.
- Using a most package in order to deploy NAS system such as samba, nfs, pacemake... Using the programming language C and shell script to develop command line for NAS System.
- Test commands line Utility and Replication for server system of vender Toshiba on virtual machine. These virtual machines are Red Hat Enterprise 6.8, 7.2 and Window Server 2012 R2. All the virtual machine installed on VMware ESXi 5.5.
- Take part in test share storage of server system though Brocade Fabric switch. The sever system using Fibre Channel protocol to share storage.
- Deploying ScaleIO v1.32 on ESXi Severs.
- Test Open Stack for server system.

Technology: C, Shell script, Linux.

01/2018 to 03/2019

Toshiba Software Development VietNam

- Implement Web API service for GridDB database server side with some APIs such as Get/Put/Delete Rows, Get container list, get container inforamtion, create container, execute sql and tql command of GridDB database,
- Test automatic UI web by Selenium
- Know basic knowledge of GitLab (commit code, create merge request to reviewer source code)
- Essential skills are Java 8, Spring Boot

Technology: Java, Spring boot, GridDB database (similar Cassandra DB)

04/2019 to 09/2019

Toshiba Software Development VietNam

- Develop Embulk open source software to transfer data from multiple database (mysql, postgresql...) to GridDB database with some feature such as
 - Tranfer data with large data Terabyte (faster than conventional methods)
 - When disconnected, you can resume data automatically

...

- Write script YAML with ANSIBLE for automatic server configuration.
- Develop Kaa Log appenders open source software for GridDB database with feature:
 - Save information from IOT device to GridDB database (such as: temperature, humidity ...)
- Test docker build/run dockerfile to automatic install for GridDB database.

Technology: Java, Ansible, Docker.

10/2019 to 04/2020

Toshiba Software Development VietNam

- Migrate Spring to Spring Boot for backends sever of GridDB database.
- Develop new command line interface use jLine1 plugin for GridDB database. (use Java 8)
- Develop 2 screen show information nodes in cluster and node detail for GridDB (use VueJS)

Technology: Java, Spring, Spring boot, VueJS and Vuetify

05/2020 to current:

- Create rpm package for GridDB WebAPI
- Fix bug with these projects Spring boot.

Education

Bachelor of Science: Hanoi University of Science and Technology - 2014

Major: Electronics and Telecommunication Engineering